<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[HEART RATE + FITNESS WRISTBANDMake every beat count with Fitbit Charge 2TM—the all-new heart rate and  tness wristband. Maximize workouts with PurePulse® heart rate, multi-sport modes and Connected GPS. Track all-day activity, exercise and sleep. And make the most of your routine with smartphone noti cations, Reminders to Move and guided breathing sessions.PUREPULSE® HEART RATEContinuous, automatic, wrist-based heart rate tracking without an uncomfortable chest strap.ALL-DAY ACTIVITY TRACKINGTrack steps, distance, calories burned,  oors climbed, active minutes and hourly activity.AUTO SLEEP TRACKINGAutomatically track how long and how well you sleep and set a silent vibrating alarm.MULTI-SPORT TRACKINGEasily record runs, biking, weights and more with real-time stats on display.CONNECTED GPSConnect Charge 2 with the GPS on your phone to see real-time stats like pace and distance on display and record a map of your route.AUTO EXERCISE RECOGNITIONSmartTrackTM automatically recognizes select exercises (running, biking and more) and records them for you in the Fitbit app.CARDIO FITNESS LEVELGet a better understanding of your  tness level and see how you can improve over time with a personalized Cardio Fitness Score.GUIDED BREATHING SESSIONSFind moments of calm throughout your day with personalized guided breathing sessions based on your heart rate.SMARTPHONE NOTIFICATIONSSee call, text and calendar noti cations on display (when your phone is nearby).REMINDERS TO MOVEGet friendly Reminders to Move that encourage you to reach an hourly goal of 250 steps.HI-RES TAP DISPLAYTap the screen to see your stats on the interactive OLED display.INTERCHANGEABLE BANDSSwitch up your look with accessory bands in leather and more.LONG BATTERY LIFEBattery life up to 5 days so you can trackall day and night without needing a charge.*WIRELESS SYNCINGSync stats wirelessly and automatically to your computer and 200+ leading iOS, Android and Windows devices.*Battery life and charge cycles vary with use, settings, and other factors; actual results will vary.MSRP $14995SPECIAL EDITION $17995SIZES S, L (XL AVAILABLE IN BLACK, ONLINE ONLY) COLORSBLACK PLUM BLUE SPECIAL EDITIONBLACK/ GUNMETALTEALLAVENDER/ ROSE GOLDWATER RESISTANT]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[PUSH YOUR FITNESS FURTHERPUREPULSE® HEART RATEUse continuous heart rate and simpli ed heart rate zones to quickly gauge exercise intensity during workouts and better track calorie burn.MULTI-SPORT + CONNECTED GPSActivate a multi-sport mode for real-time stats on display and more precise tracking.Connect to your phone’s GPS to see run stats like pace & distance, and get a post-workout map of your route in the Fitbit app.CARDIO FITNESS LEVELUsing your heart rate and exercise stats, Charge 2 gives you a Cardio Fitness Score in the Fitbit app and shows how you compare to people of your age and gender.FIND THE STYLE THAT MOVES YOUChoose the look you love with Special Edition trackersor accessory bands from our Classic and Luxe collections. Tracker not included with accessory bands.Special Edition trackersLavender/Rose Gold, Black/Gunmetal Tracker and band includedSIZES S, L$17995Classic accessory bandsBlack, Plum, Blue, TealSIZES S, L, (XL BLACK & ONLINE ONLY)Tracker sold separately $2995Luxe leather accessory bandsBrown, Blush Pink, IndigoSIZES S, LTracker sold separately $6995Take time to breathe.Guided Breathing SessionsBy tracking your real-time heart rate, these 2-minute or 5-minute sessions give you personalized prompts that help guide you through a relaxing breathing session.See the whole picture in the Fitbit app.View easy-to-read charts and graphsthat visualize your progress.Set goals, log food and track weightto understand your trends.Compete with friends and familyin challenges and on the leaderboard.Earn achievement badgesand get milestone updates.]]></page></pages></Search>