<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[FITNESS WRISTBANDMotivation is your best accessory with Fitbit Alta—a customizable  tness tracker that’s as versatile as your personal style. Automatically track activity, exercise and sleep, get reminders to move and update your look for every occasion with accessory bands.ALL-DAY ACTIVITY TRACKINGTrack steps, distance, calories burned and active minutes.AUTO SLEEP TRACKINGAutomatically track your sleep and set a silent vibrating alarm.ACCESSORY BANDSPersonalize your look with a sleek lineup of accessory bands in metal, leather and classic.REMINDERS TO MOVEOn-screen messages help you reach hourly step goals and keep you moving throughout the day.AUTOMATIC EXERCISE RECOGNITIONSmartTrackTM automatically recognizes select exercises and records them for you in the Fitbit app.CLOCK + TAP DISPLAYSee stats and time with an easy-to-read OLED tap display, and customize your clock face and layouts.SMARTPHONE NOTIFICATIONSSee call, text and calendar noti cations on display (when your phone is nearby).LONG BATTERY LIFEWear your wristband up to 5 full days and nights without needing a charge.WIRELESS SYNCINGSync stats wirelessly and automatically to your computer and 200+ leading devices.INSPIRE + COMPETEConnect with friends and family by sharing stats, sending direct-messages and competing on the leaderboard or in Fitbit Challenges.MSRP $12995SIZES S, L, XL (ONLINE ONLY) COLORSBLACK PLUM BLUE TEALWATER RESISTANT]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[GET PERSONAL PEP TALKSTo keep you on track toward better health, Fitbit Alta can send you reminders to move throughout the day. On-screen messages encourage you to reach mini-goals of 250 steps per hour and cheer you on when you do.NEVER MISS A WORKOUT WITH SMARTTRACKAutomatically track exercises like walks, runs and elliptical sessions, then open the app to see a summary of your workout and how you’re stacking up toward your weekly exercise goals.FIND A STYLE THAT FITSCreate the right accessory for any occasion—from work to workouts and beyond— with accessory bands from our Classic or Luxe collections. Tracker not included.Classic bandsBlack, Plum, Blue, TealSIZES S, L, XL (Black only) $2995Luxe leather bandsGraphite, Blush PinkSIZES S, L $5995Luxe metal bandStainless SteelSIZE S $9995Track your progress with mobile & online tools.See easy-to-read charts and graphsthat track your progress.Set goals, log food and track weightto see a more complete picture of your health.Compete with friends and familyin challenges and on the leaderboard.Earn achievement badgesand get milestone updates.]]></page></pages></Search>