<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[GoPro BulletinPRO QUALITY CAPTURE. SIMPLY THE BEST.Capturing 4K Ultra HD video and liquid-smooth slow motion at up to 240 frames per second,1 HERO4 Black delivers higher performance than any other GoPro.4K30 / 2.7K601 / 1440p80 fps 1080p120 / 960p120 / 720p2401 12MP / 30 fps BurstControl / View / Share ProtuneTM now for Photo + Video SuperViewTMAuto Low Light Waterproof to 131’ (40m)KEY FEATURES• 2x more powerful image processor2• 2x faster video frame rates,2 including 4K30, 2.7K601 and 1080p120 fps• 12MP photo capture up to 30 fps• Built-in Time Lapse Video capture1• Professional low-light performance• High-performance audio with increased dynamic range2 • HiLight Tag lets you mark key moments while recordingfor easy playback, editing and sharing• Built-in Wi-Fi and Bluetooth® support the GoPro App, Smart Remote3 and more1May require a camera so ware update. 2Compared to the HERO3+ Black Edition. 3Sold separately.]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[GoPro BulletinOTHER HOT ITEMSLCD TOUCH BACPACTM (3rd Generation)This removable touch display seamlessly attaches to the back of your GoPro, and makes it easy to frame shots, play back videos and photos, and quickly adjustcamera settings.3-WAYTM Grip | Arm | TripodThis 3-in-1 mount can be used as a camera grip, extension arm, or tripod. The folding arm makes it possible to capture selfies without the mount appearing in the shot. The handle doubles as a grip, and stores a lightweight, mini tripod.DUAL BATTERY CHARGER + BATTERY (for HERO4)Conveniently charges two HERO4 camera batteries simultaneously. Includes a spare 1160mAh lithium-ion rechargeable battery for your HERO4 camera.Note: For charging specifications, see the Important Product + Safety Information Guide included with the Dual Battery Charger.GET TRAINED ON GOPRO BRAND, PRODUCTS AND TECHNOLOGY AND EARN UP TO 40% OFF RETAIL.GET STARTED• Visit gopro.com/training• Sign in by entering your Member ID and Password• Or click Sign Up and follow the prompts to become a memberSee more at partner.gopro.com3000 Clearview Way | San Mateo, CA 94402Actual product specifications may vary, and all features, functionality and other product specifications are subject to change without notice or obligation. GoPro, HERO and their respective logos are trademarks of GoPro, Inc., in the United States and other countries. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners. Copyright © 2015. GoPro, Inc. All rights reserved.]]></page></pages></Search>