<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[FITNESS WRISTBANDMeet Fitbit Flex 2—an ultra-slim, swim-proof  tness wristband with a removable tracker that  ts into bands, bangles or pendants, so you can track all-day activity, exercise and sleep in a style that’s all your own.ALL-DAY ACTIVITY TRACKINGTrack steps, distance, calories burned, active minutes, hourly activity and hourly activity.SWIM-PROOFWear it in the shower, ocean or pool. Track swimming automatically and see workout summaries in the Fitbit app.INTERCHANGEABLE ACCESSORIESStyle the ultra-slim, removable tracker by hiding it inside wristband, bangle and pendant accessories..AUTO SLEEP TRACKINGAutomatically track how long and how well you sleep and set a silent vibrating alarm.AUTO EXERCISE RECOGNITIONSmartTrackTM automatically recognizes select exercises like runs and bike rides and records them for you in the Fitbit app.REMINDERS TO MOVEGet friendly Reminders to Move that encourage you to reach an hourly goal of 250 steps.SMARTPHONE NOTIFICATIONSGet call and text noti cations with unique vibration patterns and color-coded lights.LED DISPLAYTap to see progress to your daily goal, and see the display light up when you get calls, texts & Reminders to Move.LONG BATTERY LIFEBattery life up to 5 days so you can trackall day and night without needing a charge.*WIRELESS SYNCINGSync stats wirelessly and automatically to your computer and 200+ leading iOS, Androidand Windows devices.INSPIRE + COMPETEShare your stats and compete with friends on the leaderboard, and in Fitbit Challenges.MSRP $9995ONE SIZE (INCLUDES 1 SMALL & 1 LARGE BAND) COLORSBLACK LAVENDER MAGENTA NAVY SWIM-PROOF*Battery life and charge cycles vary with use, settings, and other factors; actual results will vary.]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[SWIM-PROOFWear Flex 2 in the pool, shower or ocean and never worry about making a splash. Plus, automatically track your swimmingand get stats like duration and calories burned.STAY CONNECTED TO YOUR DAYThe LED display gives you motivating reminders and smartphone noti cations through unique vibrations and color-coded lights.CALLS TEXTS SILENT REMINDERS GOAL ALARM TO MOVE CELEBRATIONSTYLE IT YOUR WAY WITH ACCESSORIES.A removable tracker design makes it a breeze to transform your Flex 2 from day to night, workout to wedding and beyond. Tracker not included.Luxe metal banglesSilver, Gold, Rose Gold SIZES S, LSilver $8995Gold or Rose Gold $9995Classic bandsBlack, Navy, Magenta, LavenderBlush Pink, Gray, YellowSIZES S, L $1495Luxe pendants*Silver, GoldONE SIZE – 17” chain Silver $7995Gold $9995Classic band 3-packsSport Pack – Includes Navy, Gray, Yellow Pink Pack - Includes Magenta, Lavender, Blush PinkSIZES S, L$2995*Certain features like auto sleep tracking and SmartTrack may be disabled in the pendant.See the whole picture in the Fitbit app.View easy-to-read charts and graphsthat visualize your progress.Set goals, log food and track weightto understand your trends.Compete with friends and familyin challenges and on the leaderboard.Earn achievement badgesand get milestone updates.]]></page></pages></Search>