<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[SMART FITNESS WATCHGet  t in style with Fitbit Blaze—a smart  tness watch designed to help you maximize every workout and every day with revolutionary features like PurePulse heart rate, Connected GPS, on-screen workouts, smartphone noti cations and more.PUREPULSETM HEART RATEContinuous, automatic, wrist-based heart rate tracking with no uncomfortable chest strap.CONNECTED GPSMap your routes and see real-time stats like pace and distance (when your phone is nearby).ON-SCREEN WORKOUTSGet FitStar workouts right on your wrist, with graphics to coach you along.MULTI-SPORT TRACKINGEasily record runs, cardio, biking and more with real-time stats on display.AUTOMATIC EXERCISE RECOGNITIONSmartTrackTM automatically recognizes select exercises and records them for you in the Fitbit app.ALL-DAY ACTIVITY TRACKINGTrack steps, distance, calories burned,  oors climbed and active minutes.AUTO SLEEP TRACKINGAutomatically track your sleep and set a silent vibrating alarm.COLOR TOUCHSCREEN + CLOCK FACESEnjoy a vibrant hi-res color touchscreen with multiple clock faces to choose from.SMARTPHONE NOTIFICATIONSSee call, text and calendar noti cations on display (when your phone is nearby).MUSIC CONTROLAdjust your volume and play, pause or switch songs from your smartphone with a simple tap.ACCESSORY BANDS + FRAMESChange your look with a sleek lineup of bands and frames in metal, leather and more.WIRELESS SYNCINGSync stats wirelessly and automatically to your computer and 200+ leading devices.SHARE + COMPETEShare your stats and compete with friends on the leaderboard or in Fitbit Challenges.MSRP $19995SIZES S, L, XL (ONLINE ONLY) COLORSBLACK PLUM BLUEWATER RESISTANT]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[EXPERIENCE FITNESS ON A WHOLE NEW LEVELPUREPULSE HEART RATESee continuous heart rate and simpli ed heart rate zones to quickly gauge exercise intensity during workouts.CONNECTED GPSMap your routes and see real-time run and bike stats on display (when your phone is nearby).ON-SCREEN WORKOUTSGet step-by-step instructions and graphics that coach you through FitStar workouts on your wrist.MULTI-SPORT + SMARTTRACKActivate a multi-sport mode for real-time stats on display and more precise tracking, or let SmartTrack automatically record select exercises for you, like runs and rides.FIND A STYLE THAT FITSCreate the perfect watch for any occasion with accessory bands from our Classic or Luxe collections. Tracker not included.Classic bandsBlack, Plum, BlueSIZES S, L, XL (Black only) $2995Luxe leather bands with frameBlack, Camel, Mist GreySIZES S, L $9995Luxe metal band with frameStainless Steel ONE SIZE $12995Track your progress with mobile & online tools.See easy-to-read charts and graphsthat track your progress.Set goals, log food and track weightto see a more complete picture of your health.Compete with friends and familyin challenges and on the leaderboard.Earn achievement badgesand get milestone updates.]]></page></pages></Search>