<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Advanced Fitness TrackingTracking your step count, calories burned,  oors climbed, sleep quality and more makes your goals easier to achieve. Plus, the Gear Fit2 allows you to monitor your heart rate every second of your workout.1Standalone GPSLeave your phone behind and map your run right from your Gear Fit2. Easily check your progress with daily on -screen activity summaries.Standalone Music PlayerStore music on the Gear Fit2 and enjoy your favourite workout playlists without your smartphone. Connect Gear Fit2 to a Bluetooth speaker or headphones (sold separately) and off you go.1Caution! The information gathered from this device or its related software is not intended for use in the diagnosis of disease or other conditions, or in the cure, mitigation, treatment or prevention of disease. The accuracy of the information and data provided by this device and its related software, including heart rate readings, may be affected by factors such as environmental conditions, skin condition, speci c activity performed while wearing the device, settings of the device, user con guration/user provided information, placement of the sensor on the wrist, and other end-user interactions. Please refer to the user manual for more information on proper wear and use.2IP68 rating means it’s water-resistant in up to 5 feet of water for up to 30 minutes; rinse residue/dry after wet. See user manual.Auto and Multi Sport TrackingForget about the start button. The Gear Fit2 recognizes your activity after 10 minutes whether you’re sleeping, running, cycling, working out on the elliptical or a variety of other activities. Select the appropriate activity mode and it begins tracking strength training, yoga, pilates and more.Smart Noti cationsYou’ll never miss a beat because everything gets delivered right to your Gear Fit2. Receive noti cations for your favorite apps and even respond to calls, texts and more—all without reaching for your phone.Designed to Help You Get Fit Your WayThe curved 1.5” full-color Super AMOLED display lets you easily read real-time activity reports in the sun or shade. The water-resistant2 Gear Fit2 is up for anything—no matter how sweaty or rainy your workout gets.]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[TOP DEMOSAccess the Status Menu by swiping from the top down.Access No  ca ons by swiping from right to le .STANDALONE MODEAccess the widgets by swiping from le  to right.Back Bu on.Home Bu on.Double press the home bu on to access the device se ngs, 24 Hour log and more.CHANGE / STYLISE WATCH FACEQuickly change the watch face to suit your mood, out t or amount of information you want displayed.1. Long press the Gear Fit2 home screen.2.Swipe left and right to view the various watch face options.3.Tap on the watch face that you’d like to use.-or-4. Select “Stylise” to modify awatch face to your taste.You can also download andcontrol the watch face fromthe Gear Manager. Select“Watch faces” from the menu to access more.TRANSFER MUSICEnjoy music while you work out without having to carry your smartphone. Simply pair the Gear Fit2 to Bluetooth headphones or speakers and get in your groove.1. From the Gear Manager app, select “Send Music to Gear”.2.Select the albums, artists or playlists that you want to send to your Gear Fit2.3.Tap “Done” and the music will begin transferring. 4.Repeat these steps until the Gear Fit2 has all the tracksthat you want to have with you on the go.You can also choose to “Auto Sync” your favourite, most played, recently added or other playlist, so you’ll always have the latest music with you on the go.Start tracking your  tness goals right out of the box without connecting Gear Fit2 to a smartphone.1. Remove the Gear Fit2 from the box and turn it on. 2.Scroll to the bottom of the pairing screen and tap “Usegear without phone connection”.3.Set the language and agree to the EULA. 4.Create a PIN that will be used for backing up andrestoring data.5.Set the date / time and click the next arrow. Gear Fit2 isnow ready to track your activity.You can pair Gear Fit2 to an android device at a later date and all the activity that has been tracked can then be backed up to S Health app.START EXERCISEGear Fit2 will auto detect your workout after 10 minutes of activity, but if you want to keep track of your progress from the start you can initiate your workout manually.1. Swipe to the exercise widget. It will automatically display your last work out type and duration. If your doing the same workout you can just tap “start”.If you are doing a different workout, tap the display and select your activity type and target, and select if you want the location data to be collected and how often you’d like to be “coached”. (“Guide at Intervals” setting.)Speci cations 1.5” Curved Super AMOLED Display (216 x 432) Exynos 3250 (Dual 1GHz) 4 GB Storage Sensors: Barometer, Accelerometer, Light, Heart Rate Connectivity: BT 4.1, GPS, Wi-Fi  Standalone Mode Android KitKat 4.4 and higher with 1.5 GB RAM Battery Life: 3-4 days  S Health App 4.5 x 51.2 x 11.7mm 29g]]></page></pages></Search>