<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[vívofit®3 Total steps & distance estimate, calories burned, heart rate and zone when paired withHRM, Auto Step Goal, Floors Climbed, and Activity TimerMove IQAutomatically recognizes activities - tracks walking, running, biking, swimming and elliptical training during the day without needing to start a timed activityRecord activities with or without a heart rate monitor, or using a bike speed sensor Backlit Display shows activity data and time of dayWater resistant to 50 meters (5ATM)Over One Year Battery LifeAutosyncSyncs with mobile devices automatically throughout the dayMove Bar with Audible AlertDisplays a red move bar after one hour of inactivity. Additional segments appear each 15 minutes of inactivity.Intensity MinutesMonitor your progress against aerobic activity goals recommended by health organizations such as the American Heart Association.Band OptionsMany sculpted, and color band options availableCompatible with ANT+ USB Stick to sync with a Mac or Windows PC (Not Included) Holds 3 weeks of data (12 days of data when paired with HR monitor for 1hr/day)Activity Tracking]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[vívofit® Features • Personalized daily goal is calculated based on data you enter at setup (i.e. currentactivity level: low, medium, high) and adjusts daily per activities tracked.Inactivity Meter – Move Bar:• A red move bar appears on the display after one hour of inactivity and builds when you’ve been sitting too long. Just walk for a couple of minutes to reset the move bar.Sleep Tracking Mode:• Detects movement while you sleep and when synced with Garmin Connect users will see a graph of movement throughout the night.HRM Compatibility:Auto-Goal:•zones. Using a heart rate monitor with vívofit to record heart rate and zone data willWhen used with a compatible heart rate monitor, displays heart rate and heart rateachieve more accurate calorie burn information for any fitness activity, such as a run or a cardio class at the gym.]]></page></pages></Search>