<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[UPC Code:818279015218Model Number:CHDHX-501Simply the best GoPro, ever.HERO5 Black is the most powerful and easy-to-use GoPro ever, thanks to its 4K video, voice control, one-button simplicity, touch display and waterproof design. Smooth stabilized video, crystal-clear audio and pro-quality photo capture combine with GPS to make HERO5 Black simply the best GoPro. Directly upload footage to your GoPro Plus cloud account for easy access on your phone.1WHAT’S INCLUDED12345FEATURES + BENEFITSConvenience• A single press of the Shutter button powers the camera on and starts recording automatically.• Durable by design, HERO5 Black is waterproof to 33ft (10m) without a housing.• Preview and play back your shots, change settings and trim your footage, all on your GoPro.• Enjoy hands-free control of your GoPro using simple voice commands.Connected• Bluetooth and Wi-Fi make it easy to stay connected with GoPro apps, accessories and more.• Capture the location where your photos and videos are taken.1. HERO5 Black Camera2. The Frame (HERO5 Black)3. Rechargeable Battery (HERO5 Black) 4. Mounting Buckle5. Curved + Flat Adhesive Mounts6. USB-C Cable (not shown)Capture Quality• Stunning 4K video and 12MP photos in Single, Burst and Time Lapse modes.• HERO5 Black captures stunningly smooth video handheld, mounted to your favorite gear, and more.• HERO5 Black automatically filters out wind noise.• Advanced image processing provides stunning video and photo quality in low-light conditions.• Advanced audio processing captures left and right stereo audio channels.• RAW photos provide the most flexibility when using advanced photo editing software.• WDR Photo captures added detail in shadows and highlights in the scene.• Fine-tune exposure settings with simple on-screen Exposure Control.The Versatile GoPro Family• Charge HERO5 Black up to 20% faster2 with the optional GoPro Supercharger (International Dual-Port Charger).• Capture life in a whole new way with 30+ GoPro mounts and accessories, including KarmaTM, 3-WayTM, Remo and more.Footnotes1GoPro Plus is a subscription service available in select territories. Cancel anytime. Automatic upload to the cloud requires connection to an AC power plug (not included), full battery charge and GoPro Plus membership. Visit gopro.com/plus for info and availability.2Charging performance may vary based on charging conditions.PHOTO12MP / 30 FPSBURST / TIME LAPSEVIDEO4K30 / 1440p80 / 1080p12033FT (10M)WATERPROOFSIMPLE ONE-BUTTON CONTROLWI-FI + BLUETOOTH®ADVANCED WIND NOISE REDUCTIONVOICE CONTROLVIDEO STABILIZATIONTOUCH DISPLAYAUTO UPLOAD TO CLOUDGPS LOCATION CAPTURERAW + WDR PHOTOSSee more at partner.gopro.com3000 Clearview Way | San Mateo, CA 94402Actual product specifications may vary, and all features, functionality and other product specifications are subject to change without notice or obligation. GoPro, HERO, Karma and their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of GoPro, Inc. in the United States and other countries. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners. Copyright ©2016. GoPro, Inc. All rights reserved.]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[VIDEORESOLUTION4K2.7K2.7K (4:3) 1440p 1080p960p720p 480p/WVGAPHOTOPHOTO + NIGHT PHOTO 12MP (Wide)GOPRO APPSFPS (NTSC/PAL)30,1 25,1 2460,2 50,2 48,2 30, 25, 24230, 2580, 60, 50, 48, 30, 25, 24120,3 90,1 80,4 60, 50, 48, 30, 25, 24 120, 60, 50240,5 120, 100,4 60, 50, 30,7 257 240BURST12MP @ 30 fpsFIELD OF VIEW (FOV)SuperViewTM, WideSuperView, Wide, Medium, LinearWideWideSuperView, Wide, Medium, Linear, Narrow WideSuperView, Wide, Medium, NarrowWideTIME LAPSE0.5, 1, 2, 5, 10, 30, 60 second intervalsFootnotes1Available in Wide FOV only.2Available in Wide, Medium and Linear FOV only. 3Available in Wide and Narrow FOV only. 4Available in SuperView FOV only.5Available in Narrow FOV only.6Available in SuperView and Wide FOV only. 7Available in Wide, Medium and Narrow FOV only.NIGHT LAPSEAuto (default), 4, 5, 10, 15, 20, 30 second intervals;1, 2, 5, 30, 60 minute intervalsCapture and create stunning videos on the go. Our mobile and desktop apps make it easy. Get the free GoPro apps at gopro.com/apps.CAPTURELive preview, playback + full camera control.QUIKTMAwesome edits made easy.QUIK | DesktopAuto import and upload your footage to the cloud. Simple storytelling tools and a large library of soundtracks make it easy to create awesome videos.]]></page></pages></Search>