<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi Smart ScaleKnow where you stand. Get where you want to be.With the Fitbit Aria scale, you’ll have an accurate picture of your long term weight trends by tracking your weight, % body fat and body mass index (BMI) over time.The Aria scale is a high-end performance scale that measures weight, % body fat, and BMI. With a few clicks of easy setup, Aria will upload directly to your home wireless network and sync your information automatically each time you step on the scale. And why keep your favorite device to yourself? You can invite up to 7 household members to set up an account. While you get better acquainted with your stats, Aria will automatically recognize you from the others in your household.Fitbit ’s online tools and apps provide a complete weight management system. Weight management begins  rst with understanding where you stand by tracking your weight, % body fat, and BMI with charts and graphs over time to see weight trends. To keep you motivated, Fitbit has designed a host of online tools, like food and  tness logging, badges to earn, the option to connect and share progress with friends, and the ability to set, track and achieve your weight goals.All information is defaulted to private; however, you can select your own settings for your Aria stats by going to your device's privacy settings on Fitbit.com.DisplayWeight and % body fatUPC CodeWhiteFB201W 898628002038BlackFB201B 898628002045Packaging sizeHeight12.3 inches (31.2 cm)Width12.3 inches (31.2 cm)Depth1.3 inches (33.4 mm)Weight4 lbs, 4.3 oz (1.93 kg)System requirementsOperating systems Mac OSX 10.5, 10.6, 10.7 XP, Vista, Windows 7+Mobile setup iPhone, iPod Touch, iPad running iOS 4, 5 AndroidWindows Mobile 7+For more information, visit www. tbit.com]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[What if all your health metrics were in one place, accessible through your smartphone or online? With Fitbit, you can create one central hub to easily capture, analyze and understand your everyday health. Fitbit also integrates over a dozen popular apps like LoseIt, Runkeeper, and Endomondo. Fitbit is committed to deliveringsimple, innovative health and  tness products and services that  t seamlessly into people’s lives to inspire every day change. Fitbit products help people lead healthier, more active lives by giving them the tools to become more aware, more motivated and more  t every day.Uploads wirelesslyEffortlessly uploads to Fitbit.comTracks weight, % body fat, and moreTracks weight, % body fat, and BMIMulti-UserRecognizes up to 8 usersEasy setupReady in minutes, Aria is easy to set up and connect onlineFree web and mobile appsAccess your free account with Fitbit’s free web, iPhone, and Android appsCharts and GraphsSet weight goals, log food, and workouts with free online tools. Track trends to see or analyze progress.Connect and ShareConnect with friends and family for support or to compete.BadgesEarn badges to celebrate weight management achievements.For more information, visit www. tbit.com]]></page></pages></Search>