<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?><Search><pages Count="2"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[GoPro BulletinSO SMALL. SO STOKED.HERO4 Session packs the power of GoPro into our smallest, lightest, most convenient camera yet. Its rugged, waterproof design eliminates the need for a separate housing, while a single button powers on the camera and starts recording automatically. With 1080p60 video and 8MP photos, HERO4 Session delivers the professional image quality that has made GoPro famous.1440p30 / 1080p60 fps 960p60 / 720p100 fps 8MP / 10 fps Burst Control / View / Share ProTuneTM for Video Auto Low Light Waterproof to 33’ (10m)KEY FEATURES• Smallest, lightest GoPro yet• Durable and waterproof to 33’ (10m), no housing needed• Easy one-button control, power up and capture videos orphotos with a single press• Professional quality up to 1440p30, 1080p60 and 720p100 video• 8MP photos with 10 fps Burst• Access all camera modes and settings with the free GoPro App or Smart Remote1• Built-in Wi-Fi and Bluetooth®• Camera can be rotated in the included frames for ultraflexible, compact mounting• Compatible with GoPro mounts and accessories1Sold separately.]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[GoPro BulletinOTHER HOT ITEMSFLOATY For HERO4 SessionThis easy-to-spot flotation wraps around your HERO4 Session to keep it afloat. It’s specially designed to protect your camera, while also giving you easy access to the shutter button. Floaty is perfect for worry-free shooting in and around the water while surfing, snorkeling, wakeboarding and more.THE STRAP Hand + Wrist + Arm + Leg MountStrap your GoPro to your hand, wrist, arm or leg to capture hands-free ultra immersive POV footage, one-of-a-kind selfies and more. Includes an extended strap that fits around your arm, leg or larger objects. Features 360° rotation and tilt that let you adjust your capture angle on the fly.CASEY Camera + Mounts + Accessories CaseCasey is the perfect GoPro travel and storage solution. It fits inside a backpack, but is large enough to carry your HERO cameras, mounts and accessories. The water-resistant, semi- rigid shell guards against light rain and snow. A padded interior protects your camera, while removable dividers let you create customized compartments.GET TRAINED ON GOPRO BRAND, PRODUCTS AND TECHNOLOGY AND EARN UP TO 40% OFF RETAIL.GET STARTED• Visit gopro.com/training• Sign in by entering your Member ID and Password• Or click Sign Up and follow the prompts to become a memberSee more at partner.gopro.com3000 Clearview Way | San Mateo, CA 94402Actual product specifications may vary, and all features, functionality and other product specifications are subject to change without notice or obligation. GoPro, HERO and their respective logos are trademarks of GoPro, Inc., in the United States and other countries. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners. Copyright © 2015. GoPro, Inc. All rights reserved.]]></page></pages></Search>